Jamie Lynn

Javascript Python Fullstack Web Developer

Coppell, Tx 75019 (972) 440-9156 toby2494@hotmail.com seolynn.com Jamielynn.dev https://github.com/feeby2494

With a Passion and Child-like curiosity of building things and learning the underworkings of systems, I love building full-stack applications with Python and Javascript. My pass experience in device repair along with my management experience, I believe I have many transferrable skills. With the right company and team, we can share our passion and love of web development together.

PROJECTS

Django App for Web Project submission

For my freelance business offering Data Analysis and Web Development. Possible to send orders in with multiple projects, two step registration, and user login/logout features.

Links: Live Site Github

Django Vue Blog

A Simple Django Restframework / Vue Blog with images, iframes, and many elements per post possible.

Links: <u>Github-backend</u> <u>Github-frontend</u>

Mobile Repair Mail-in Service Version 2

Planned to replace Seolynn.com with Django/Vue app for faster development and more optimized/stable code. Less custom code.

Links: Github-backend Github-frontend

seolynn.com— Mobile Repair Mail-in Service

Site I use for online repair business. Possible to submit device for repair, users can login to see their devices along with progress. Admin can view all devices and change status of devices. Flask with React used.

Links: Live Site Github-FullStack

chromebooks.v3.jamielynn.dev— *Chromebook and Macbook parts Reference and Inventory Management Application*

One of my first Flask/React apps I made to tackle the issue my repair team was facing at AGi Repair. I needed a centralized app to look up part numbers for chromebooks and macbooks. Later added inventory that corresponds to physical location codes on shelves. Dealt with Json Web Tokens for user authentication.

Links: Github, Live Site

jamielynn.dev— *Personal Site*, *Language Learning Tools*, *and Portfolio* My personal Flask/React site. Have not worked on it for a while. Have two apps to help

me learn Korean and Japanese.

SKILLS

513 Grace Ln

React.js, Flask, Django, Vue.js, Wordpress, PHP, Nginx, Linux, Bash, Digital Oceans, Rest API, Node, Docker, Javascript, Python,Mysql, Postgres, SQLite3, Sqlalchemy, Git, Jinja, HTML, CSS

LANGUAGES

English (Native), Korean (Intermediate Beginner), Japanese (Beginner)

EDUCATION

University of North Texas, Denton, Tx — *Bachelors or Arts*

Aug 2011 - Aug 2015

My love for learning Japanese and Korean, and my love of history brought me to a difficult, but necessary descion in my life. While I was struggling with math and physics, I changed my major twice finally deciding on International Studies. Liberal Arts major fit me the best and I loved studying about language, culture, religion, people, international aid, and history.

Coursera, Online — Google *Certificates*

Jan 2020 - Oct 2022

- Google IT Authentication Certificate (Certificate Link)
- Google IT Help Desk Certificate (<u>Certificate Link</u>)
- FreeCode Camp JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures (Certificate Link)
- Meta Backend Developer Certificate (4 out of 9 completed)

PAST WORK EXPERIENCE

AGi Repair Tx, Carrollton, Tx — Chromebook Tech (was Facility Manager)

Nov 2016 - Dec 2022

- Built Flask / React application for my team
- Led Computer repair team, then the whole office (around 15 employees)
- Researched advanced micro-soldering repair techniques to teach team

I worked myself up from iPad tech to computer repair lead, then to assistant manager (only one month!), then to facility manager, then everything fell apart. My issue with management is I'm too nice to my employees and don't like putting my fist down. I also didn't have the time needed to learn managing people well. From assistent manager to head of the Texas office in only a month was too fast for me! Recent downturn in the repair bussiness and some mistakes on my part resulted in my demotion and eventual lay off.

When I was lead I created the chromebook/macbook inventory application to tackle the problems my team was having with looking up part numbers and keeing physical inventory. I was not a part of the official development team, but because I made this app for a business issue and my office used it, I consider this professional experience.

Ministry of Education, Science and Technology, Jeonju-shi, Jeollabuk-do, Korea(the one everyone loves) — *TALK Scholar*

2013 - 2015

- Helped Engish Teacher in morning times
- Taught afterschool class
- Helped students with their conversation skills
- Immersed students in Western culture
- Learned and used as much Korean as possible

My love of Korea eventually brough me here as part of the TaLK program (Teach and Learn in Korea). TALK scholar is an English Teaching Assistant and Afterschool Teacher. I used Korean as much as I could, but hit some limits in my ability with the language. I plan to build up my grammar and vocabulary, then take the TOPIK certifications. I loved and still love Korea and the Korean language, but teaching English wasn't for me. With that said, my greatest memories in life were in Korea.